proxybonanza.com 2015-03-24

# Cookies & Privacy

  * Home
  * Plans & Pricing 
  * How it Works
  * About
  * Contact

In order to be able to render Services to the Customer, and as a result of using Services by the Customer, SC Media Limited Liability Company Limited Partnership (SC Media Sp. z o.o. Spolka Komandytowa) with its registered seat in Lodz, Beskidzka 143 street, Poland, hereinafter referred to as Proxybonanza.com will collect certain personal information about visitors who access Proxybonanza.com web site. The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to the Customers what types of information Proxybonanza.com will collect and how that information will be used.

  1. **Confidentiality**  
The Customer's privacy and confidentiality of any data received from the Customers is of highest importance to Proxybonanza.com. Therefore Proxybonanza.com does not provide, sell, rent, or lease (except where required by law) the personal information of our users to any parties outside of Proxybonanza.com. Furthermore Proxybonanza.com undertakes not to sell our Customer's personal information to third parties for commercial or marketing purposes. All the information Proxybonanza.com collects only in purpose of rendering Services to our Customers. 
  2. **Collection of Personal Data**  
On the basis of the Article 18 of Act on Electronic Services (Ustawa o swiadczeniu uslug droga elektroniczna z dnia 9 wrzesnia 2002 r. Dz. U. 2002, nr 144, poz. 1204) Proxybonanza.com is entitled to collect following information from the Customer: 
    1. Name and family name
    2. Residence address
    3. E-mail addresses
    4. Other data necessary for rendering Services

Proxybonanza.com collects personal data from the Customer at the moment the Customer fills in the form which is available on Proxybonanza.com web site. By filling in the form with personal data the Customer acknowledges that Proxybonanza.com will have an access to these data and will use it in order to render Services as well as in order to demand and receive payment of fees from the Customer.

The Customer has a right to access to his personal data at any time as well as a right to make amendments.

Any information which Proxybonanza.com may collect from the Customer through correspondence with Proxybonanza.com, whether via email, by telephone or by written letter, will only be used to address matters within that correspondence. If this requires referring such correspondence to a third party to ensure customer service, the Customers personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address his query or concerns, and will otherwise be kept confidential.

Proxybonanza.com retains logs containing information about access made to and through Proxybonanza.com services for 30 days. The only purpose for which these information are used is the calculation of the actual transfer of data and determination of potential abuse feasor in case of abuse complaint. Proxybonanza.com may be obliged to reveal such information to the authorities and other bodies to which the binding law gives powers to demand such information.

  3. **Public Space (Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third Party Web Sites)**  
Any information that the Customer disclose in a public space, including on any bulletin board, chat room or any site accessed through Proxybonanza.com server, is available to anyone else who visits that space. Proxybonanza.com cannot safeguard any information which was disclosed there and hence cannot be held responsible.
  4. **Site Linking**  
Proxybonanza.com web site may contains links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to Proxybonanza.com. Proxybonanza.com cannot protect any information the Customer may disclose on these sites and recommends that the Customer reviews the relevant privacy policy statements of those sites. Proxybonanza.com cannot be held responsible for any use of the Client's personal information arising from disclosure of personal information on third party sites. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Proxybonanza.com web site.
  5. **Disclosure of personal data**  
Proxybonanza.com reserves the right to disclose information about the Customer and all personal data which the Customer revealed to Proxybonanza.com whenever required to do so by law, or in order to exercise Proxybonanza.com legal rights or defend Proxybonanza.com against legal claims. Proxybonanza.com reserves the right to disclose the Customer's personal information in case the Customer has given his explicit legal written consent to do so.
  6. **Modifications to Privacy Policy**  
It may be necessary from time to time, to amend or modify this Privacy Policy. Proxybonanza.com reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy or update it. Amendments will be posted on Proxybonanza.com website and will become binding after 14 days after posting. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates.
